<Publish>
	<ModId Value="120143" />
	<DisplayName Value="Extractors Begone" />
	<ShortDescription Value="Controls sub-building and work vehicle spawning for extractor areas in specialized industries." />
	<LongDescription>
This mod allows to customize two aspects of extractor areas in specialized industries:

* It allows to set the spawn rate for extractor sub-buildings, including to disable them altogether by setting the rate to `0.0`.
* It can disable the spawning of work vehicles within the extractor areas.

It supports all currently available types of specialized industry, including farming, forestry, oil, ore and fishing.

The main benefits of this mod (especially compared to the traditional method of creating narrow mazes of extractor areas) are:

* it's more convenient to use,
* it does not reduce industry output (which depends on the extractor area size),
* it allows to disable work vehicles as well.

### Setup

After installing the mod, simply load into your savegame or start a new game. By default, all extractor buildings and most work vehicles (except fishing boats) are disabled. Work vehicles will immediately despawn automatically. You can remove already spawned extractor sub-buildings from the mod's menu in the game menu. By clicking the "Despawn Extractors" button, all extractors will be despawn, except in those industries for which you set a non-zero spawn rate. You may even try to disable the extractor area spawn system altogether, which may get handy for future industry additions or other types of area spawnables (those include storage and cargo areas). However, keep in mind that this may have unintended side effects.
		
Besides disabling extractor buildings, this mod also allows you to toggle spawning work vehicles on a per-industry level. You can access the corresponding settings from the game menu, too.

### Uninstalling
		
The spawn rates are potentially stored into your savegames. To make sure to safely remove the mod, load into your savegame first, then reset the spawn rates to their default values (`2.0`, or just use the corresponding button). Save the game afterwards before ultimately uninstalling the mod.
		
If you somehow missed resetting the spawn rates and are left wondering how to get extractors spawning back into your existing industries, simply re-install the mod and follow the procedure described above.

### Sources and Feedback

The source code for this mod is available at [GitHub](https://github.com/crud89/CS2-ExtractorsBegone/). If you encounter any issues with this mod, or want to leave feedback, please [head over there as well](https://github.com/crud89/CS2-ExtractorsBegone/issues)!
	</LongDescription>
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/screen00.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/screen01.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/screen02.jpg" />
	<Tag Value="" />
	<ForumLink Value="" />
	<ModVersion Value="1.1" />
	<GameVersion Value="1.0.*" />
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<RequiredDLC Value="" />
	<ChangeLog>
**Version 1.1**

- Add settings in main menu
- Add controls for per-industry spawn rates
- Add controls for per-industry vehicle toggles
- Add button to quickly remove existing extractor buildings
- Fix issue with existing work vehicles not automatically despawning
- Fix issue with trucks getting stuck in harbors
- Fix issues with cargo and storage buildings not working
		
**Version 1.0**

Initial Release.
	</ChangeLog>
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/crud89/CS2-ExtractorsBegone" />
</Publish>