<Publish>
	<ModId Value="120143" />
	<DisplayName Value="Extractors Begone" />
	<ShortDescription Value="Disables sub-buildings and work vehicles for extractor areas." />
	<LongDescription>
		This mod disables two in-game systems:

		* The area spawn system is used to spawn extractor and storage sub-buildings.
		* The work car AI system, which controls cars that spawn within extractor areas.

		Note that this also includes the specialized industries from the Bridges and Ports DLC (inland and offshore fishing), as they share the same systems.

		Those sub-buildings and vehicles are purely visual though! The resource simulation itself is handled independently and resources will still accumulate in the central buildings over time and are transported from there. Overall, disabling those sub-buildings is a great option, if you want to fully customize your farms, quarries, mines and so on. It might even marginally improve performance, but don't expect miracles.

		This mod disables those systems altogether. It is not possible to only disable them per industry, nor is there a UI at the moment.

		As always, use this at your own risk. Back up your savegames and test this in an fresh city first. It should work with existing saves and uninstalling the mod should restore the original functionality.

		After installing this mod you can (and might want to) remove existing sub-buildings and work vehicles using the better bulldozer mod. Work vehicles and boats will not despawn, when this mod is used with a savegame where they are already spawned! After installing this mod, I recommend to immediately pause the savegame after first loading into it and remove all work vehicles. They will continue to drive to their last destination, where they will get stuck. Normally you can remove them there, but I noticed that when the last destination was the central industry building, the vehicles sometimes aren't clickable from better bulldozer, making them stuck there forever.
	</LongDescription>
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/screen01.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/screen02.jpg" />
	<Tag Value="" />
	<ForumLink Value="" />
	<ModVersion Value="1.1" />
	<GameVersion Value="1.0.*" />
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<RequiredDLC Value="" />
	<ChangeLog>
**Version 1.1**

- Added settings UI
		
**Version 1.0**

Initial Release.
	</ChangeLog>
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/crud89/CS2-ExtractorsBegone" />
</Publish>